{
    "id": "34e3f947e61a4b24a56d1f275a8901d2",
    "title": "Common word combinations exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "91ded2cd6aa44d8a80a287c5565efec7",
            "title": "Common Word Combinations",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": ". I despair .................................... reforming that fellow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "about",
                        "of",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Never deviate ..................................... the path of truth.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "with",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "This plan radically differs ...................................... the earlier one.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "from",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am diffident .................................... passing the TOEFL this time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "about",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I entirely disagree .................................... you on this point.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "with",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are a disgrace ................................... your whole family.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish to dispose ......................................... my old car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "of",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I tried to dissuade him ....................................... following such a course of action.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "from",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His father is disgusted ..................................... him for his addiction to gambling.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "with",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Although this is similar to the other one, it is quite distinct ..................................... it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "from",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}